♪The phone number I remember by heart♪
♪ رقم الهاتف الذي أذكره في القلب ♪
♪You stopped answering all my calls♪
♪ لقد توقفت عن الإجابة على كل اتصالاتي ♪
♪Does it cause trouble for your new relationship♪
♪ هل يسبب مشكلة بعلاقتك الجديدة ♪
♪Those photos of us I kept♪
♪ تلك الصور لنا التي احتفظت بها ♪
♪I kept them because I wouldn't let go of the past♪
♪ احتفظت بها لأن لن أتخلى عن الماضي ♪
♪It was just a habit to cling to each moment♪
كانت مجرد عادة للاعتماد على كل لحظة ♪
=Captain Han=
= النقيب هان =
=Episode 22=
= الحلقة 22 =
Well,
إذن
they're fine.
إنه بخير
We're relieved.
نحن مرتاحون
Wu Wen, half a year ago, you were Captain Han's love rival.
وو وين، قبل نصف عام كنت منافس حب النقيب هان
How did you suddenly
كيف أصبحت فجأة
become their love guardian?
أصبح ولي حبهما؟
They've gone through so much.
لقد مرروا بالكثير
After everything,
بعد كل شيء
I realized
أدركت
what difficulties facing them.
ما هي الصعوبات التي يواجهونها
Well,
إذن
aren't you the same?
ألست متشابهًا؟
Yes.
نعم
I heard when the police came,
سمعت عندما أتت الشرطة
you were the first one to rush in.
كنت أول من أسرع في ذلك
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
Don't you realize it?
ألا تدركين ذلك؟
If the ricin powder was real,
إذا كان مسحوق الأرز حقيقيا
and you rushed in without any protection,
وأنت هرعت دون أي حماية
your life would be risky.
ستكون حياتك محفوفة بالمخاطر
Are all journalists
هل جميع الصحفيين
so reckless?
متهورة إلى هذا الحد؟
What are you laughing at?
ما الذي تضحكه؟
Stop it.
توقف
Forget it.
انس الأمر
Yes, it's my fault.
نعم، هذا خطأي
I'll try to be cautious.
سأحاول أن أكون حذرًا
That's more like it.
هذا أحسن
Tonight, we don't need to stay here.
الليلة، لا نحتاج إلى البقاء هنا
Shall we find a place
هل نجد مكانا
to have a drink?
لاحتساء مشروب؟
Okay, let's drink.
حسنًا لنشرب
But I need
لكنني بحاجة
to change clothes first.
تغيير الملابس أولا
Wu Wen.
وو وين
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
It doesn't look good?
ألا يبدو جيدًا؟
I'm not used to dressing like this.
لست معتادًا على ملابس كهذه
But the clothing store owner said
لكن صاحب مخزن الملابس قال
it looked good.
بدا جيدًا
I'll go up and get changed.
سأصعد لأتغير ملابسي
Wait for me.
انتظرني
It looks great. Wait for me.
يبدو رائعًا، انتظريني
For the past six months,
خلال الأشهر الستة الماضية
I've been like this,
لقد كنت هكذا
working hard on reports
والعمل بجد على إعداد التقارير
and do interviews.
وتجري المقابلات...
I don't have to tell you about each of my interviews, do I?
لا داعي لأن أخبرك عن كل مقابلة من مقابلاتي، صحيح؟
No need. I've seen them all.
لا حاجة، رأيتها كلها
Your every video report
كل تقرير فيديو لك
and news article,
ومقالات إخبارية
I've seen or read them all.
رأيتها أو قرأتها جميعا
It's a pity you're not a host and don't broadcast news.
من المؤسف أنك لست مضيفة ولا تبث الأخبار
Otherwise, I could see you every day.
خلاف ذلك، كان بإمكاني رؤيتك كل يوم
When you were not around,
عندما لم تكن بجانبي
I always imagined
كنت أتخيل دائما
what you were doing
ما كنت تفعلين به
without me.
من دوني
I worked hard every day,
عملت بجد كل يوم
filling up my schedule
ملء جدولي الزمني
to stay busy.
للاستمرار في العمل
In this way, I won't have the time to miss you.
بهذه الطريقة لن يكون لدي الوقت لأفتقدك
But I failed.
لكنني فشلت
When I took a 10-minute nap,
عندما أخذت قيلولة لمدة 10 دقائق
I dreamed about you.
حلمت بك
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة
I'm scared of not overcoming obstacles,
أخشى ألا أالتغلب على العقبات
letting us live in guilt
السماح لنا بأن نعيش مذنبا
and pain.
والألم
I'm sorry. I've brought you more sorrow
أنا آسف، أحضرت لك المزيد من الحزن
than happiness.
من السعادة
So in the days to come,
لذا في الأيام القادمة
let's live in happiness, okay?
دعنا نعيش في سعادة، اتفقنا؟
Sorry to barge in.
آسفة عن اقتحامها
Can I borrow the flowers
هل يمكنني استعارة الزهور
on your table?
على طاقتك؟
It's too late now, and I can't buy any.
فات الأوان الآن، ولا يمكنني شراء أي منها
- Of course, you can.
- بالطبع يمكنك ذلك
When did it happen?
متى حدث ذلك؟
What's going on with Wu Wen?
ماذا يجري مع وو وين؟
Why hasn't he come back yet?
لماذا لم يعد بعد؟
Xiya, I'm really sorry.
شياو جيا، أنا آسف حقا
It's too late, and the flower shop is closed.
فات الأوان ومحل الزهور مغلق
You look so beautiful today.
تبدين جميلة جدًا اليوم
You should receive flowers.
يجب أن تتلقى الزهور
I remember you like yellow.
أتذكر أنك تحبين الصفراء
So I picked out all the yellow ones
لذلك اخترت كل الأصفر
from Nannan's flowers
من أزهار نان
for you.
لك
Let's go.
لنذهب
Here.
هنا
Thank you.
شكرًا لك
Cheers, come on.
هيا
What's going on with them?
ماذا يجري معهم؟
Something must be going on.
لا بد أن شيئًا ما يجري
They're all here for the party.
جميعهم هنا من أجل الحفل
Why haven't you come yet?
لماذا لم تأتي بعد؟
I haven't finished my report yet.
لم أنتهي من تقريري بعد
Are you drinking?
هل تحتسي الكحول؟
A bit.
قليلا
Send me the address.
أرسليه العنوان
I'll come to pick you up now.
سآتي لإصطحابكم الآن
Han Xizhou.
هان شيتشو
Come on. I won't get drunk
بحقك، لن أثمل
after only one beer.
بعد جعة واحدة فقط
I know,
أعرف
but I miss you.
لكنني اشتقت إليك
I want to see you right now.
أريد أن أراك الآن
So can you tell me the address now?
هلّا أخبرتني العنوان الآن؟
Okay.
حسنًا
Wait for me.
انتظرني
You're here.
أنت هنا
Did you drink a lot?
هل احتسيت الشراب كثيرًا؟
No, just a bit.
لا، قليلًا فقط
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes.
نعم
Nannan, I really missed you tonight.
ننان، اشتقت إليك حقًا الليلة
But we saw each other in the daytime.
لكننا رأينا بعضنا في اليوم
But you wasted so much time.
لكنك أهدرت الكثير من الوقت
Let's go. They are waiting for us.
هيا بنا هم في انتظارنا
Cheers.
النخب
Han Xizhou.
هان شيتشو
I came back in a hurry,
عدت في عجلة من أمري
so I didn't pack many things.
لذلك لم أحزم الكثير من الأشياء
What do you need? I'll take you to buy it.
ماذا تفعلين؟ سآخذك لشراء ذلك
I know a place
أعرف مكانًا
where it has everything I need.
أين يوجد كل ما أحتاج إليه
Where?
أين؟
Your house.
منزلك
So, are you taking me home?
هل ستأخذني إلى المنزل إذًا؟
Hold on.
تمسكي
♪You make me smile and touched♪
♪ أنت تجعلني أبتسم وتأثر ♪
♪We cheer up each other♪
♪ نحن تشجع بعضنا البعض ♪
♪Please don't hesitate anymore♪
♪ أرجوك لا تتردد بعد الآن ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to come closer♪
♪ في انتظارك أن تقترب ♪
♪Don't miss each other again, and don't be shy anymore♪
♪ لا تشتاق لبعضكما البعض مرة أخرى ولا تكوني خجولة ♪
♪Hold hands together and travel around♪
♪ أمسكي بيدي معًا والسفر ♪
Thank you for coming back to me.
شكرًا لك على عودتي
♪Out of my own will♪
♪ خارج إرادي ♪
♪Be it sunny or rainy♪
♪ كن مشوشا أو ماطلا ♪
♪Further and further away♪
♪ مزيد من المسافة ♪
♪The dusk extends deeper♪
♪ الغبار ممتد بعمق ♪
♪After all these years♪
♪ بعد كل هذه السنوات ♪
♪My look won't expose my longing♪
♪ مظهرني لن يفضح شقتي ♪
♪I've never changed♪
♪ لم أتغير أبدا ♪
♪Wish all your dreams come true♪
♪ هل تتحقق كل أحلامك ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪I've been obsessed with you once♪
♪ لقد كنت مهووسة بك مرة واحدة ♪
♪Freedom is my customized label♪
♪ الحرية هي بطاقة التعريف الخاصة بي ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪Your smile fades away with time♪
♪ ابتسامتك تتلاشى مع الوقت ♪
♪Seeing you going away with her♪
♪ أمنحك بالخروج معها ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪I've been obsessed with you once♪
♪ لقد كنت مهووسة بك مرة واحدة ♪
♪Freedom is my customized label♪
♪ الحرية هي بطاقة التعريف الخاصة بي ♪
♪How I wish it was just a delusion♪
♪ كيف أتمنى لو كان مجرد خداع ♪
♪Your smile fades away with time♪
♪ ابتسامتك تتلاشى مع الوقت ♪
♪Seeing you going away with her♪
♪ سيأخذك بعيدا معها ♪